♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ You and I go hard at each
other like we're going to war ♪
♪ You and I go rough, we
keep throwing things ♪
♪ And slamming the doors ♪
♪ You and I get so damn dysfunctional ♪
♪ We stopped keeping score ♪
♪ You and I get sick, yeah ♪
♪ I know that we can't do this no more ♪
♪ Yeah but baby, there you go
again, there you go again ♪
♪ Making me love you ♪
♪ Yeah, I stopped using
my head, using my head ♪
♪ Let it all go ♪
♪ Got you stuck on my body,
on my body like a tattoo ♪
♪ And now I'm feeling stupid ♪
♪ Feeling stupid crawling back to you ♪
♪ So I cross my heart, and I hope to die ♪
♪ That I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ And I know I've said
it a million times ♪
♪ But I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ Try to tell you "No" ♪
♪ But my body keeps on telling you "yes" ♪
♪ Try to tell you "Stop" ♪
♪ But your lipstick got
me so out of breath ♪
♪ I'll be waking up in the
morning, probably hating myself ♪
♪ And I'll be waking
up, feeling satisfied ♪
♪ But guilty as hell ♪
♪ Yeah but baby, there you go
again, there you go again ♪
♪ Making me love you ♪
♪ Yeah, I stopped using
my head, using my head ♪
♪ Let it all go ♪
♪ Got you stuck on my body,
on my body like a tattoo ♪
♪ And now I'm feeling stupid ♪
♪ Feeling stupid crawling back to you ♪
♪ So I cross my heart, and I hope to die ♪
♪ That I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ And I know I've said
it a million times ♪
♪ But I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ Yeah, baby, give me one more night ♪
♪ But baby, there you go
again, there you go again ♪
♪ Making me love you ♪
♪ Yeah, I stopped using
my head, using my head ♪
♪ Let it all go ♪
♪ Got you stuck on my body ♪
♪ On my body like a tattoo, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ So I cross my heart, and I hope to die ♪
♪ That I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ And I know I've said
it a million times ♪
♪ But I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ So I cross my heart and I hope to die ♪
♪ That I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ And I know I've said
it a million times ♪
♪ But I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
♪ I dunno, whatever ♪